{
    "subject": "resource/Caesar_and_Cleopatra_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United Kingdom",
    "human_readable": "The country where Caesar and Cleopatra (film) was produced is United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9281168580055237,
            "question": "In what country was the film 'Caesar and Cleopatra' produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9208395481109619,
            "question": "Name the country that produced the film 'Caesar and Cleopatra'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8969129323959351,
            "question": "Which country's film industry produced 'Caesar and Cleopatra'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8766279220581055,
            "question": "What is the production country of the movie 'Caesar and Cleopatra'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.81034255027771,
            "question": "Where was 'Caesar and Cleopatra' made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7796821594238281,
            "question": "Which country is associated with the making of 'Caesar and Cleopatra'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7682588696479797,
            "question": "What is the production nation of the movie 'Caesar and Cleopatra'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7489732503890991,
            "question": "Where was 'Caesar and Cleopatra' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6874317526817322,
            "question": "Can you tell me the country of origin for the movie 'Caesar and Cleopatra'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6849762201309204,
            "question": "What nation was responsible for making the film 'Caesar and Cleopatra'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The country where Caesar and Cleopatra (film) was produced is United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6600_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the country of origin for the movie 'Caesar and Cleopatra'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6600_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was 'Caesar and Cleopatra' filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6600_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the production nation of the movie 'Caesar and Cleopatra'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6600_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6600_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6600_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6600_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6600_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6600_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6600_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6600_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6600_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6600_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6600_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the document with file path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6600/re-ranker-msmarco/65.txt states \"Directed by Gabriel Pascal \u2022 1945 \u2022 United Kingdom\", which indicates that the film \"Caesar and Cleopatra\" was indeed produced in the United Kingdom."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the film \"Caesar and Cleopatra\" was directed by Gabriel Pascal, produced by Gabriel Pascal Productions, and filmed in Technicolor with lavish sets. They also specify that the production was reported to be the most expensive film ever made in Britain at the time. Therefore, the statement that the country where Caesar and Cleopatra (film) was produced is the United Kingdom is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}